jarkey.net 2006-12-23

# Privacy Statement

WEB ENTERTAINMENT PRODUCTIONS, INC. PRIVACY POLICY

Web Entertainment Productions, Inc. we appreciates our relationship with you, respects that your information is yours, and is committed to safeguarding your privacy when you’re using our web site. The following describes our collection of and use of any information that we may collect from you.

**Questions**

If you have any questions, we can be reached via [e-mail](mailto:jarkey_games@yahoo.com).

**We generally do not collect any information.**

For each visitor to our Site, our web server does not recognize any **** information regarding the visitor’s domain or e-mail address. We only collect information that you voluntarily provide to us.

**We do not use Cookies but our third party advertisers might use Cookies.**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable us to recognize your computer and to deliver personalized features. The information collected by cookies is sometimes called “clickstream” or “click trail” and may also describe which areas of the Site you have used. We do not use cookies at this time. However, in the course of serving advertisements to this Site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.  We do not receive any such information from our third party advertisers nor do we have any control over such third party advertisers or the use of any such information that is collected.

**We collect certain information if you request our Newsletter.**

We collect electronic mail information only if it is volunteered by you, such as your specific request to be added to our Newsletter mailing list. The information we collect from you if you subscribe to our Newsletter is used only to email the Newsletter to you.

**We may amend this Privacy Policy.**

If in the future this Privacy Policy is amended or updated, you will be subject to this Privacy Policy as amended or updated.  We will not notify you of any amendments or updates to this Privacy Policy.  It is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy often for any changes hereto.

copyright 2005  Web Entertainment Productions, Inc.  All Rights Reserved.
